museglobal.com 2007-12-25

# MuseGlobal -- Privacy Policy

  |    |   | 

At MuseGlobal Inc., we are committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. When you encounter a screen in this site that asks for information you do not want us to have or use, you should not proceed further with that screen. 

## Collecting your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are asked to order e-mail newsletters, or request information from us, or use our online customer support services for your library. Personal information collected by MuseGlobal Inc., often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested. 

## Security of your Personal Information

MuseGlobal Inc., strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under circumstances where this policy would violate a lawful court order and/or Federal, State, or Local law or Statue. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where MuseGlobal Inc., its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located. 

## Protection of Children's Personal Information

The MuseGlobal Inc., site does not publish content that is targeted to children. 

## Use of Cookies

Cookies allow Web browsers to remember information from a Web site. The browser stores the information in a text file. The message is then sent back to the site each time the browser requests a page from the site. A cookie can only be accessed by the site that created it. You can reset your browser so that it will refuse cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the MuseGlobal Inc., Web site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you may not experience a personalized visit. 

MuseGlobal uses cookies to record customer assent. We do not use cookies for storing passwords or other sensitive information. 

## Log Files

Each view of a page on this site is logged. We record information such as the most requested pages, usage by country, most downloaded pages, most active organizations, etc. This information is used solely to gather broad demographic information for analysis of web site usage in improving services to our customers. This information is not shared outside of the company. 

## Consent and Changes to the Privacy Policy

Your use of this site implies your consent to the collection of the information described in this policy. When changes are made to this policy, MuseGlobal will post these changes to this page of the website so that you will be aware of the information we collect and how we use it. 

## Contact Information

MuseGlobal Inc., welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please contact us. 

Regards, 

Webmaster  
MuseGlobal Inc. 

|
